In the question hash string,
鉴于 hash_string 问题
we have to determine which of the following statements are true.
我们将确定下面的哪些说法是正确的
Let's go through the statements 1 by 1.
让我们一个一个地看这些说法
The first statement says the number of string comparisons done to look up a keyword
第一个说法是查询哈希表里没有的关键字
that is not a key in the hash table may be less than the number needed to look up a keyword
所需要进行字符串比对次数可能小于
that is a key in the hash table.
查询哈希表内含有的关键字的次数
As this turns out, this is actually a true statement.
实际上 这确实是正确的说法
In order to show it, we need an example,
我们举个例子来说明
so let me give you an example dictionary with 3 buckets and 3 keywords in here.
在这里 我给出一个有3个桶和3个关键字的字典实例
I'm not showing the values because they don't really matter for this example.
我没有给出哈希函数的值是因为对于这个例子来说它们无关紧要
It could be the case that if we search for "Batman"
当我们搜索 "Batman" 时就是说法1为真的情况
our hash function takes us to bucket 0
哈希函数找到0号桶
and then we have to compare between "Andy," "is," and finally "Batman."
然后我们不得不将关键字分别和 "Andy" "is"比对 最后再和 "Batman" 比对
So that would be 3 string comparisons.
所以这需要3次字符串比较
Let's say we search for "Irvin" and that brings us to bucket 2.
而当我们搜索 "Irvin" 时 我们找到2号桶
There's nothing in bucket 2, so there's no comparisons to be made.
2号桶是空的 所以一次比较也不用做
This is an example where it actually takes more comparisons
这就是那个查询哈希表内的数据所需要的比对次数确实大于
to look up something in the hash table than it does to look up something not in the hash table.
查询不在哈希表里的数据需要的比对次数的例子
Statement 2 says we should expect the time to look up most keywords in the hash table
第二个说法是我们可以预测当我们增加哈希桶的数量时
will decrease as we increase the number of buckets.
搜索大多数关键字的时间将会减少
And with a good hash function this is true.
在有一个好的哈希函数的情况下 这是正确的
Let's say we have a hash table with only 2 buckets.
假设我们有一个只包含两个桶的哈希表
If we have a good hash function, the number of keywords in each bucket is the same.
如果我们有一个好的哈希函数 那么在每个桶里的关键词的数量是一样的
And so the average number of comparisons is going to be half the size of a bucket
为了搜索哈希表里的某个关键词
in order to look up a keyword in the hash table.
进行比较平均次数应该是桶的大小的一半
If we double the number of buckets, the average lookup time is decreasing significantly.
如果我们将桶的数量增加一倍 平均搜索时间明显减少
And with a good hash function the time is going to decrease even more.
在有一个好的哈希函数的情况下 搜索时间减少地更多
Statement 3 says it is always better to have more buckets in a hash table.
第三个说法是在哈希表中 桶的数量总是越多越好
This is a pretty strong statement,
从使用"总是"这个词语可以看出
as indicated by the use of the word always,
这是一个相当绝对的说法
and it's really because of that word that the statement is false.
但正是因为"总是"这个词语导致这个说法是错误的
There's really 2 good reasons.
这有两个很好的原因
The first reason is because changing the number of buckets,
第一个原因是随着桶的数量的变化
be it more or less, changes where keywords hash to.
或多或少地会改变关键字的索引位置
It could be the case that with 2 buckets I have a good distribution.
这样一种情况可能发生 在两个桶的情况下 关键词的分布合理
But if I add a third bucket, the hash function is such
但是当我增加第三个桶后
that everything lands in that new bucket.
哈希函数将所有的关键词放到新桶中
We choose hash functions carefully so that this is less likely,
我们仔细选择哈希函数使这种情况很少发生
but depending on the keywords you're using, this is still possible.
但是取决于我们正在使用的关键词 这种情况仍然有可能出现
And the second reason is memory.
第二个原因是内存
I could have an arbitrarily long hash table,
我可以有一个任意长的哈希表
but they can use a lot of space, especially if there are a few keywords that go into it.
但是它将会占用大量的空间 尤其是表里只有少量关键词的时候
Real-world implementations of hash tables try to shoot for a ratio
靠谱的哈希表实现力争得到
between the number of buckets they have and the number of keywords,
哈表内桶的数量和关键词数量的比值
increasing the number of buckets accordingly
这样 随着哈希表内关键词的数量的增加和减少
as the number of keywords in the hash table decrease and increase.
相应地增加桶的数量
Statement 4 says the time to look up a keyword in the hash table
第四个说法是 在哈希表中搜索一个关键字的时间
is always less than the time it would take in a linear time list (as used in Unit 4).
总是小于在线性表(正如第四单元用过的)中搜索所花费的时间
So the question is, is the lookup time always less
问题是 搜索时间总是小于
than the lists that we've been using previously?
搜索我们以前使用过的列表所需要时间?
And as you might suspect, this statement is false.
正如你怀疑的那样 这个说法是错误的
We're going to show that by giving an example hash table.
我们将给出一个哈希表实例来证明
If I have a hash table where 3 keywords all go in bucket 1,
假设我们有一个3个关键词全部在1号桶的哈希表
if I want to look up the keyword "Batman," I'm going to go to bucket 1
如果我想查找关键字"Batman" 我会找到1号桶
and iterate through each item in this bucket until I find "Batman."
接着遍历桶中的每个关键字直到我找到"Batman"为止
That's essentially the same as a normal list where we just start from the beginning
这本质和我们不做任何哈希变换
without doing any kind of hash function
从头开始一个一个遍历每个关键字来查找"Batman"
and just go through each item 1 by 1 searching for "Batman."
的普通列表是一样的